# Sagar Kishor Pandya

Add: E/908 9th floor, Aryan one, Shirgaon, Opp Kalp nisarg, Badlapur (E.), Thane-421503. Contact no: 9768086689 Email id: Sagarpandya065@gmail.com.

## **Career Objective**:

To associate myself with a challenging role in an organization which promises professionalism and independence of working methodology, where my knowledge and experience will be utilized fully for attaining the organization goals and in return I would be benefitted with self-development and enriched with skills and experiences.

## **Educational Qualification**:

Qualification	University/College	Year
Graduate (BCOM)	S.K . Somaiya/ Mumbai University	2016
H.S.C	N.K.T College /Maharashtra board	2013
S.S.C	Dyandeep Vidyamandir / Maharashtra board	2011

#### **Additional Information**:

MS-Office (Word, Excel)

## Interpersonal Skill:

- Ability to lead people in different situation.
- Determinant and hardworking.
- Maintain patience during complex situation

#### **Work Experience:**

Company: Gebbs healthcare solutions

Duration: April 2016 - Nov 2017

**Designation:** Associate

Key Role Area: AR calling, denial code posting, follow up on denial, Authorization denial.

Company: Net India PVT.LTD

**Duration:** November 2017 - January 2020

**Designation:** Senior Associate

Key Role Area: AR calling, denial code posting, , Patient calling and Authorization denial.

**Company**: Navigant BPM

**Duration**: January 2020 - December 2020

**Designation**: Senior Associate

**Key Role Area**: Job profile - AR calling, follow up on denial.

**Company**: Gebbs Healthcare Solutions from.

**Duration**: December 2020- Present **Designation**: Senior Associate

Key Role Area: Billing enteral therapy claims to MEDICARE

Personal details

Gender: - Male

Date of birth:- 24 January 1996

Marital Status: - Unmarried

Nationality: - Indian

Languages Known: - English, Hindi, Marathi & Gujrati

Mother name : - Yajurveda Pandya

.